

Details

8493671118 arialdyscv@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Dominican

Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React

Selenium

Cypress

Postman

JAVA

Git

Languages

Spanish Native

English C1

Profile

Adaptable person with the ability to learn quickly. Passionate about software development looking forward to become a great developer and contribute with my knowledge and willing to learn more. JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, JAVA, SQL, GIT, are some of the technologies that I can handle. Also have more than 2 years performing manual tests

Employment History

QA Automation - Newtech, Santo Domingo

2022 — PRESENT

•Perform and verify test cases with the help of different tools and frameworks to make them automated.

Project Consultant - at EmpowerHR, Santo Domingo

2019 - 2022

- Consultant for Web App Payroll123.
- Provided solutions within the system for the clients
- · Process changes as per client request
- Performing QA testing for web app changes.
- Implemented Payroll123 and its modules for new clients.

QA Tester – Caribbean Telecom & Solutions, Santo Domingo

2017 — 2019

- Manual testing for web apps and websites.
- · Unit, integral and regression testing.

Education

Software Engenieer, Universidad del Caribe (UNICARIBE), Santo Domingo

Architecture, Universidad Autónoma de Santo Domingo, Santo Domingo

Courses & Certifications

Certified Scrum Developer (CertifPro)

2022

React Developer (Udemy)

2022

Computer Science Fundamentals (Kodigo)

2022

C# .NET, Instituto Tecnológico Las Americas (ITLA)

2019

Fundamentals of Programming, Instituto Tecnológico Las Americas (ITLA)

Java Certification, Escuela de Organization Industrial (EOI)

2019